Evelyn B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Daniel B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
about O
Amazon B-COMPANY
from O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zadar B-CITY
u O
Australije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Vodafoneu B-COMPANY
. O

Olivia B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
flew O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
to O
Sydney B-CITY
to O
visit O
Meta B-COMPANY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Pfizera B-COMPANY
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Sara B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
o O
Atlassianu B-COMPANY
u O
Hong Kongu B-CITY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
thanked O
Oliver B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
for O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Denver B-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Petaru B-PERSON
Babiću I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Vodafonea B-COMPANY
u O
Splitu B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
San Mateo B-CITY
u O
Nizozemskoj B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Alexander B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
about O
Siemens B-COMPANY
from O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Gabrijela B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Jelena B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Microsofta B-COMPANY
u O
Parizu B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
i O
Tea B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Appleu B-COMPANY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Andrejem B-PERSON
Pavlovićem I-PERSON
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Irske B-COUNTRY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Ava B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
about O
TikTok B-COMPANY
from O
Vancouver B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
joined O
UBS B-COMPANY
in O
Birmingham B-CITY
after O
leaving O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
, O
Gabrijela B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Šibenik B-CITY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
i O
Lea B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
u O
Finske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Appleu B-COMPANY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
met O
Luna B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
presented O
Shopify B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
in O
Toronto B-CITY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
met O
Emma B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
in O
Johannesburg B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
sent O
SAP B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
in O
Vancouver B-CITY
. O

Daniel B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
sent O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Ella B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
about O
Citi B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Samsunga B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
and O
Daniel B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
discussed O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Sydney B-CITY
, O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Ženeva B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Siemensu B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Dora B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Parizu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Netflix B-COMPANY
, O
Elijah B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
from O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Applea B-COMPANY
, O
Mario B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Rijeka B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
SAP B-COMPANY
, O
Amelia B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
moved O
to O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
from O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
joined O
Intel B-COMPANY
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
after O
leaving O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
presented O
BP B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Mila B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
thanked O
Sophia B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
for O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Geneva B-CITY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Marko B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
iz O
Sydneyu B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
met O
Michael B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
in O
Lisbon B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Aiden B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
about O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
from O
Zurich B-CITY
, O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Dubrovnik B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Microsoftu B-COMPANY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
sent O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Lucas B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
in O
Boston B-CITY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
HSBC B-COMPANY
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
sent O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Matthew B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Marija B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Metaa B-COMPANY
u O
Beču B-CITY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
sent O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
in O
Toronto B-CITY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Petar B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
o O
Shellu B-COMPANY
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
. O

Ava B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Avery B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
about O
Visa B-COMPANY
from O
Lisbon B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
to O
Seattle B-CITY
to O
visit O
Siemens B-COMPANY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Jacob B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
about O
Netflix B-COMPANY
from O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Sara B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Citia B-COMPANY
u O
Toulouseu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Netflix B-COMPANY
, O
Mason B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Vancouver B-CITY
from O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
and O
Alexander B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
discussed O
Intel B-COMPANY
's O
and O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
presented O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Henry B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
in O
London B-CITY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
about O
BP B-COMPANY
from O
Reading B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

William B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
visited O
Rome B-CITY
in O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
UBS B-COMPANY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Pula B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Lea B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
u O
Beču B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Italije B-COUNTRY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
visited O
Vancouver B-CITY
in O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
IBM B-COMPANY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marin B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Indije B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Janko B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
iz O
Sydneyu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
i O
Dora B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Rimu B-CITY
u O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Nvidiau B-COMPANY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Zoran B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Ella B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
about O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
from O
Johannesburg B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Lausanne B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Arapskih I-COUNTRY
Emirata I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Appleu B-COMPANY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
thanked O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
for O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Edinburgh B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
and O
Harper B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
discussed O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Amazon B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Manchester B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Prag B-CITY
iz O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Amazonu B-COMPANY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Helena B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
o O
Appleu B-COMPANY
u O
Lisabonu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Samsung B-COMPANY
, O
Sophia B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Johannesburg B-CITY
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Sara B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Filip B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
iz O
Zadru B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
sent O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Olivia B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
in O
Seoul B-CITY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
and O
Olivia B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
discussed O
Shell B-COMPANY
's O
and O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Toronto B-CITY
, O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
visited O
Prague B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Accenture B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
UBS B-COMPANY
, O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
HSBC B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
i O
Petra B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Readingu B-CITY
u O
Irske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
BP-u B-COMPANY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Matija B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Oraclea B-COMPANY
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
to O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
to O
visit O
Spotify B-COMPANY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
sent O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
William B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Emma B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
about O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
i O
Ela B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Münchenu B-CITY
u O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Airbusa B-COMPANY
u O
Readingu B-CITY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Nestléa B-COMPANY
u O
Münchenu B-CITY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
visited O
Seattle B-CITY
in O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Airbus B-COMPANY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
Zagrebu B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
thanked O
Noah B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
for O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
i O
Luka B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Teslau B-COMPANY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Johannesburg B-CITY
u O
Južnoafričke B-COUNTRY
Republike I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Spotifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Marin B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
iz O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
u O
Rimu B-CITY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Spain B-COUNTRY
to O
Zurich B-CITY
to O
visit O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Marija B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
o O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

Daniel B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
sent O
Oracle B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
in O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
and O
Emily B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
discussed O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Google B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Sydney B-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Airbusa B-COMPANY
u O
Dublinu B-CITY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Lausanne B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Deloitteu B-COMPANY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zürich B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Siemensu B-COMPANY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Atlassiana B-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Ante B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Pfizera B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
thanked O
Benjamin B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
for O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Mario B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
iz O
Pragu B-CITY
u O
Južnoafričke B-COUNTRY
Republike I-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
, O
Mason B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Austin B-CITY
from O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Lea B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Vodafonea B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marin B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Japana B-COUNTRY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Shopifya B-COMPANY
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Dublin B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Citiju B-COMPANY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
flew O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
to O
Phoenix B-CITY
to O
visit O
Shopify B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Google B-COMPANY
, O
Olivia B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
moved O
to O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
from O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Mirna B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Apple B-COMPANY
, O
Noah B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Lausanne B-CITY
from O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Amsterdam B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Arapskih I-COUNTRY
Emirata I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
. O

Prema O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
, O
Leon B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
London B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
visited O
Dublin B-CITY
in O
Australia B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
TikTok B-COMPANY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Emma B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
about O
BP B-COMPANY
from O
Manchester B-CITY
, O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Citia B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
sent O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
in O
Seoul B-CITY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
discussed O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Roche B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Boston B-CITY
, O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
sent O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Jacob B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Infobipu B-COMPANY
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
. O

Gabrijela B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Marko B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
o O
Accentureu B-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Osijek B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Deloitteu B-COMPANY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Filip B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
u O
Parizu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
i O
Zoran B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
u O
Italije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Matej B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
iz O
Toulouseu B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Arapskih I-COUNTRY
Emirata I-COUNTRY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Teslaa B-COMPANY
u O
Beču B-CITY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Kristina B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
o O
Amazonu B-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Isabella B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
and O
Mason B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
discussed O
IBM B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Airbus B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Edinburgh B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Ava B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
thanked O
Amelia B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
for O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Manchester B-CITY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Ethan B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
about O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
from O
Miami B-CITY
, O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Intel B-COMPANY
, O
Ethan B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Miami B-CITY
u O
Nizozemske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Oliver B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
about O
HSBC B-COMPANY
from O
Stockholm B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Kristina B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
o O
Metau B-COMPANY
u O
Johannesburgu B-CITY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
to O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
to O
visit O
Barclays B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
presented O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Olivia B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
in O
Denver B-CITY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
visited O
Birmingham B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Airbus B-COMPANY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
i O
Lea B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
u O
Irske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Samsunga B-COMPANY
u O
Johannesburgu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Airbus B-COMPANY
, O
Mia B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Miami B-CITY
from O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Filip B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
met O
Aria B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
and O
Emma B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
discussed O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Chicago B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Dora B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Japana B-COUNTRY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Josip B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
o O
Boeingu B-COMPANY
u O
Edinburghu B-CITY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Filip B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Nestléa B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Marin B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Marta B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tea B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
HSBC B-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Dora B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
iz O
Münchenu B-CITY
u O
Nizozemske B-COUNTRY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlassiana B-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marko B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
u O
Miamiju B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Nizozemske B-COUNTRY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
joined O
Samsung B-COMPANY
in O
Ottawa B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
thanked O
Mia B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
for O
Oracle B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Sara B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ante B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
iz O
Londonu B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenog B-COUNTRY
Kraljevstva I-COUNTRY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
met O
Ethan B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
in O
Zurich B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ivana B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
u O
Pragu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Mirna B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
iz O
Berlinu B-CITY
u O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
and O
Camila B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
discussed O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Tesla B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
London B-CITY
, O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
sent O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Isabella B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
in O
London B-CITY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
presented O
Shell B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Olivia B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
in O
Lisbon B-CITY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
i O
Karla B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Šibeniku B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Leon B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Matthew B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
about O
Shopify B-COMPANY
from O
Vancouver B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
i O
Josip B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Prema O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
, O
Marija B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Helsinki B-CITY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
visited O
Sydney B-CITY
in O
Germany B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Amazon B-COMPANY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Ivana B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Intela B-COMPANY
u O
Lisabonu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
, O
Mia B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
moved O
to O
London B-CITY
from O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ivan B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
iz O
Puli B-CITY
u O
Češke B-COUNTRY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Rim B-CITY
iz O
Indije B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Shopifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
joined O
Shell B-COMPANY
in O
Sydney B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Matej B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Harper B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
met O
James B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Airbusa B-COMPANY
, O
Mirna B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Reading B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Shopifya B-COMPANY
, O
Karla B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Ottawa B-CITY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Beč B-CITY
u O
Irske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Spotifyju B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Shopify B-COMPANY
, O
Jackson B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Edinburgh B-CITY
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
joined O
Netflix B-COMPANY
in O
Ottawa B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Leon B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
iz O
Sydneyu B-CITY
u O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Sydney B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Andrej B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Varaždinu B-CITY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
Alexander B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
discussed O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Oracle B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Toulouse B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Daniel B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
and O
Liam B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
discussed O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
and O
BP B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
joined O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Applea B-COMPANY
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Sophia B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
about O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
from O
Toulouse B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Dario B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
Readingu B-CITY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Ante B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

Dora B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Zoran B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
o O
Teslau B-COMPANY
u O
Johannesburgu B-CITY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Abigail B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
about O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Josip B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
o O
Oracleu B-COMPANY
u O
Pragu B-CITY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
and O
Lucas B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
discussed O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Birmingham B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
joined O
UBS B-COMPANY
in O
Boston B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
about O
IBM B-COMPANY
from O
Barcelona B-CITY
, O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
met O
Alexander B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
in O
Prague B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
thanked O
Isabella B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
for O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Prague B-CITY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
thanked O
Luna B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
for O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Birmingham B-CITY
. O

Harper B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
visited O
Tokyo B-CITY
in O
Canada B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Petar B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
HSBC B-COMPANY
u O
Rimu B-CITY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
joined O
SAP B-COMPANY
in O
Barcelona B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
thanked O
Camila B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
for O
Tesla B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Austin B-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Madrid B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Shellu B-COMPANY
. O

Sofia B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
joined O
HSBC B-COMPANY
in O
Rome B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Shopify B-COMPANY
, O
Emily B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Amsterdam B-CITY
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Nikola B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
o O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
u O
Edinburghu B-CITY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
thanked O
Abigail B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
for O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
joined O
Airbus B-COMPANY
in O
Miami B-CITY
after O
leaving O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Boeing B-COMPANY
, O
Abigail B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
and O
Oliver B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
discussed O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
to O
Vancouver B-CITY
to O
visit O
Amazon B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
met O
Jacob B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
and O
Mila B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
discussed O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Austin B-CITY
, O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
discussed O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
and O
BP B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Madrid B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zagreb B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
SAP-u B-COMPANY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Dubrovnik B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Intelu B-COMPANY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
sent O
Roche B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Ella B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
in O
Toulouse B-CITY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Metai B-COMPANY
u O
Puli B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
sent O
SAP B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Alexander B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tea B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Googlea B-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Vodafonea B-COMPANY
, O
Dario B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Varaždin B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
, O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Lisbon B-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
and O
Jacob B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
discussed O
Google B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Miami B-CITY
iz O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
New York B-CITY
iz O
Australije B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Nika B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Visaa B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

Isabella B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
thanked O
Avery B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
for O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Sydney B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Nika B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
o O
Shellu B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
SAP B-COMPANY
, O
Jackson B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Lisbon B-CITY
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Sara B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
iz O
Londonu B-CITY
u O
Indije B-COUNTRY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
and O
Camila B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
discussed O
Intel B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
, O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

James B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
met O
Amelia B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
in O
Zurich B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
thanked O
Liam B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
for O
Roche B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Madrid B-CITY
iz O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Atlassianu B-COMPANY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
sent O
Intel B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
in O
Vancouver B-CITY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Dublin B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Googleu B-COMPANY
. O

Prema O
Applea B-COMPANY
, O
Josip B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Reading B-CITY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
joined O
IBM B-COMPANY
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Jelena B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
o O
Nvidiau B-COMPANY
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Marta B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
u O
Šibeniku B-CITY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Germany B-COUNTRY
to O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
to O
visit O
Visa B-COMPANY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ela B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
iz O
Münchenu B-CITY
u O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ivan B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Južnoafričke B-COUNTRY
Republike I-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
and O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
discussed O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Tesla B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Berlin B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
and O
Aiden B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
discussed O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Lucas B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
about O
Barclays B-COMPANY
from O
Munich B-CITY
, O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Ivana B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Samsunga B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Japan B-COUNTRY
to O
Austin B-CITY
to O
visit O
Citi B-COMPANY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Berlin B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenog B-COUNTRY
Kraljevstva I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Vodafoneu B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
, O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Seoul B-CITY
from O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Jerković I-PERSON
i O
Helena B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Microsoftu B-COMPANY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Ethan B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
about O
Samsung B-COMPANY
from O
Madrid B-CITY
, O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
about O
Shopify B-COMPANY
from O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Google B-COMPANY
, O
Matthew B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Manchester B-CITY
from O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
to O
Denver B-CITY
to O
visit O
Intel B-COMPANY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
i O
Matea B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Münchenu B-CITY
u O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
to O
Helsinki B-CITY
to O
visit O
Spotify B-COMPANY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Lea B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
o O
Appleu B-COMPANY
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
discussed O
TikTok B-COMPANY
's O
and O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Amazon B-COMPANY
, O
Jacob B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
from O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
to O
Amsterdam B-CITY
to O
visit O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ivan B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Aiden B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
about O
Airbus B-COMPANY
from O
Dublin B-CITY
, O
France B-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Aiden B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
about O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
from O
Boston B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Samsung B-COMPANY
, O
Oliver B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
sent O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Jackson B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
in O
Johannesburg B-CITY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
joined O
Apple B-COMPANY
in O
Geneva B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
, O
Noah B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Berlin B-CITY
from O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Aiden B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
joined O
Samsung B-COMPANY
in O
Seattle B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Stockholm B-CITY
iz O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
BP-u B-COMPANY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
thanked O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
for O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Sara B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Amazona B-COMPANY
u O
Miamiju B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Google B-COMPANY
, O
Logan B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Munich B-CITY
from O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Miami B-CITY
u O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Accentureu B-COMPANY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Marija B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
iz O
Edinburghu B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
i O
Ivan B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Dublinu B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Johannesburg B-CITY
iz O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
. O

Marta B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
i O
Marta B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
u O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
William B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
about O
Amazon B-COMPANY
from O
Stockholm B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
visited O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
in O
India B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Visa B-COMPANY
. O

Isabella B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
sent O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
in O
Helsinki B-CITY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Vancouver B-CITY
iz O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
joined O
Boeing B-COMPANY
in O
Seoul B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
, O
Avery B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Manchester B-CITY
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Pfizera B-COMPANY
, O
Ivan B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Beč B-CITY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
sent O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Matthew B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
. O

Sofia B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
to O
Munich B-CITY
to O
visit O
Amazon B-COMPANY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Split B-CITY
iz O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Siemensa B-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Citia B-COMPANY
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
to O
Helsinki B-CITY
to O
visit O
SAP B-COMPANY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Lausanne B-CITY
u O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Citiju B-COMPANY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Nika B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
iz O
Lisabonu B-CITY
u O
Italije B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Nestléa B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Vodafoneu B-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Gabrijela B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zagreb B-CITY
u O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
presented O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Olivia B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
presented O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Emma B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
in O
Ottawa B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Citi B-COMPANY
, O
Lucas B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Austin B-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
thanked O
Emma B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
for O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Amsterdam B-CITY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Matija B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
iz O
Zürichu B-CITY
u O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
. O

Sara B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
u O
Puli B-CITY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
and O
Jacob B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
discussed O
TikTok B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Phoenix B-CITY
, O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Roche B-COMPANY
, O
Liam B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Toronto B-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Abigail B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
about O
Airbus B-COMPANY
from O
Berlin B-CITY
, O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
sent O
SAP B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Ethan B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
joined O
Meta B-COMPANY
in O
Prague B-CITY
after O
leaving O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
visited O
Austin B-CITY
in O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Netflix B-COMPANY
. O

Gabrijela B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Accentureu B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
visited O
Denver B-CITY
in O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
visited O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
in O
Spain B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Airbus B-COMPANY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlassiana B-COMPANY
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Nika B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Ujedinjenog B-COUNTRY
Kraljevstva I-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Rochea B-COMPANY
, O
Ana B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
New York B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Split B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
met O
William B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
in O
Manchester B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
sent O
Tesla B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
William B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
in O
Miami B-CITY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Teslaa B-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Isabella B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
joined O
Google B-COMPANY
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
thanked O
Aiden B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
for O
Roche B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
München B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
BP-u B-COMPANY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Ante B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
o O
UBS-u B-COMPANY
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
sent O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
in O
Seattle B-CITY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
Mila B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
discussed O
Visa B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Phoenix B-CITY
, O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
and O
James B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
discussed O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Sydney B-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Janko B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
o O
HSBC-u B-COMPANY
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Visaa B-COMPANY
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
i O
Janko B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Beču B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Nvidiau B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Mario B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
iz O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Oraclea B-COMPANY
u O
Hong Kongu B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Nestléa B-COMPANY
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
and O
Michael B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
discussed O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Shopify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Harper B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
and O
Mia B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
discussed O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Barcelona B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Mario B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
. O

William B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
about O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
from O
Lisbon B-CITY
, O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Harper B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
and O
Emma B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
discussed O
Amazon B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Phoenix B-CITY
, O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
, O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Amsterdam B-CITY
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
i O
Ela B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Jerković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
London B-CITY
u O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Siemensu B-COMPANY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
i O
Luka B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Petar B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
iz O
Stockholmu B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
. O

Mila B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
and O
Ella B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
discussed O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
joined O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
in O
Miami B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Visa B-COMPANY
, O
Sofia B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Seoul B-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Jerković I-PERSON
i O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Hong Kongu B-CITY
u O
Irske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Germany B-COUNTRY
to O
Zurich B-CITY
to O
visit O
Accenture B-COMPANY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Amsterdam B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Appleu B-COMPANY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
about O
Meta B-COMPANY
from O
Miami B-CITY
, O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Matea B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Vodafonea B-COMPANY
u O
Pragu B-CITY
. O

Sofia B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
visited O
Prague B-CITY
in O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Apple B-COMPANY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
discussed O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
sent O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
in O
Toronto B-CITY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Helena B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
u O
Münchenu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Irske B-COUNTRY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
sent O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
joined O
BP B-COMPANY
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
visited O
Paris B-CITY
in O
Italy B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Tesla B-COMPANY
, O
Sophia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Madrid B-CITY
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Leon B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Jelena B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
iz O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
joined O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
after O
leaving O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
sent O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Noah B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
in O
Manchester B-CITY
. O

Ivan B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
i O
Karla B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Johannesburgu B-CITY
u O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Harper B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
about O
Citi B-COMPANY
from O
Lisbon B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
presented O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Mila B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
about O
HSBC B-COMPANY
from O
Seattle B-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Sara B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Zoran B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Parizu B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
i O
Lea B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Šibeniku B-CITY
u O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Toulouse B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Marta B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Teslaa B-COMPANY
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
HSBC B-COMPANY
u O
Seulu B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Airbus B-COMPANY
, O
Emma B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Paola B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Shella B-COMPANY
u O
Beču B-CITY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
about O
Barclays B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
presented O
Tesla B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Noah B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
in O
Geneva B-CITY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zagreb B-CITY
u O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Atlassianu B-COMPANY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Matija B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
iz O
Ženevi B-CITY
u O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Rijeka B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
UBS-u B-COMPANY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Ava B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
about O
Citi B-COMPANY
from O
Geneva B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Olivia B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
visited O
Sydney B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Airbus B-COMPANY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
presented O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Microsofta B-COMPANY
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Dublinu B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
, O
Gabrijela B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
met O
Lucas B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
in O
Phoenix B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Marta B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
i O
Marko B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Lisabonu B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Kristijan B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
iz O
Londonu B-CITY
u O
Finske B-COUNTRY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Miami B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Barclaysu B-COMPANY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
visited O
Denver B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
IBM B-COMPANY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Matej B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Zadru B-CITY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Lausanne B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
UBS-u B-COMPANY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ante B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Južnoafričke B-COUNTRY
Republike I-COUNTRY
. O

Tomislav B-PERSON
Jerković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Vodafonea B-COMPANY
u O
Lisabonu B-CITY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
to O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
to O
visit O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Miamiju B-CITY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
met O
Daniel B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
presented O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Citiju B-COMPANY
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
joined O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
in O
Chicago B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marin B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
u O
Parizu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Irske B-COUNTRY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
presented O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
in O
Lausanne B-CITY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marta B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
u O
New Yorku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Lucas B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
about O
Apple B-COMPANY
from O
Seattle B-CITY
, O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
presented O
Intel B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
in O
Helsinki B-CITY
. O

Helena B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Googlea B-COMPANY
u O
Lisabonu B-CITY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
sent O
Shell B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Logan B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
in O
Dublin B-CITY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlassianu B-COMPANY
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
IBM B-COMPANY
u O
Toulouseu B-CITY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
met O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
to O
Vancouver B-CITY
to O
visit O
Amazon B-COMPANY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marko B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
u O
Šibeniku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
and O
Logan B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
discussed O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
and O
TikTok B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
London B-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Nestléa B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Barclaysa B-COMPANY
u O
Readingu B-CITY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
flew O
from O
India B-COUNTRY
to O
Lausanne B-CITY
to O
visit O
Citi B-COMPANY
. O

Zoran B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Zoran B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
and O
Logan B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
discussed O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
, O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
presented O
SAP B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Henry B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
in O
Austin B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
, O
Henry B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
from O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
sent O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Camila B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Pula B-CITY
u O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Boeingu B-COMPANY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
to O
Amsterdam B-CITY
to O
visit O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
joined O
Barclays B-COMPANY
in O
Paris B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Amsterdam B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Spotifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Shella B-COMPANY
u O
Parizu B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ante B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
iz O
Parizu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Shopifya B-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Rochea B-COMPANY
, O
Gabrijela B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Rijeka B-CITY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Kristina B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
UBS B-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
presented O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Charlotte B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
joined O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
in O
Berlin B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
to O
Geneva B-CITY
to O
visit O
BP B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
Emma B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
discussed O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Edinburgh B-CITY
, O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Hong Kong B-CITY
iz O
Indije B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Emma B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
about O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
from O
Chicago B-CITY
, O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Readingu B-CITY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
i O
Ela B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Rimu B-CITY
u O
Nizozemske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Microsoftu B-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
about O
Meta B-COMPANY
from O
Dublin B-CITY
, O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ivan B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
iz O
Puli B-CITY
u O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Marija B-PERSON
Rašić I-PERSON
iz O
Splitu B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Atlassiana B-COMPANY
, O
Petra B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Zadar B-CITY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
visited O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
in O
Australia B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
IBM B-COMPANY
. O

Ella B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
presented O
Visa B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Emma B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Lucas B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
about O
Intel B-COMPANY
from O
Munich B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Luka B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Parizu B-CITY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
presented O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Ava B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Infobipa B-COMPANY
u O
Zagrebu B-CITY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
visited O
Lausanne B-CITY
in O
India B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Apple B-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
joined O
Roche B-COMPANY
in O
Amsterdam B-CITY
after O
leaving O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Seoul B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Oliver B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
about O
Roche B-COMPANY
from O
Manchester B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
u O
Zadru B-CITY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Marija B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Shopifya B-COMPANY
, O
Andrej B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
London B-CITY
. O

Petar B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Matea B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
and O
Jackson B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
discussed O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
and O
BP B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Geneva B-CITY
, O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Microsofta B-COMPANY
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
visited O
Barcelona B-CITY
in O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Josip B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Metaa B-COMPANY
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
thanked O
Ethan B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
for O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Johannesburg B-CITY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Siemensa B-COMPANY
u O
Puli B-CITY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
met O
Benjamin B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Lea B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
i O
Nika B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
HSBC-u B-COMPANY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
joined O
Boeing B-COMPANY
in O
Seattle B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
presented O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Daniel B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Karla B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
o O
HSBC-u B-COMPANY
u O
Edinburghu B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
about O
Tesla B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

James B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
presented O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
William B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
in O
Dublin B-CITY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
flew O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
to O
Munich B-CITY
to O
visit O
Amazon B-COMPANY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Pula B-CITY
iz O
Japana B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Intelu B-COMPANY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Ženeva B-CITY
iz O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Visau B-COMPANY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Mirna B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
o O
Vodafoneu B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Vancouver B-CITY
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Vodafoneu B-COMPANY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Petar B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
o O
Amazonu B-COMPANY
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
London B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
sent O
Google B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Avery B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
in O
Helsinki B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
, O
Matija B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Pariz B-CITY
. O

Elijah B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
visited O
Chicago B-CITY
in O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
met O
Logan B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
in O
Seoul B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Deloittea B-COMPANY
, O
Tea B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
San Mateo B-CITY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Mason B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
about O
Tesla B-COMPANY
from O
Johannesburg B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Jelena B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
o O
Oracleu B-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
thanked O
Oliver B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
for O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Rome B-CITY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Stockholm B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
thanked O
Avery B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
for O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Vancouver B-CITY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Leon B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
iz O
Šibeniku B-CITY
u O
Italije B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
, O
James B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Helsinki B-CITY
from O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Marta B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Accenturea B-COMPANY
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Rijeka B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Nestléu B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Tokio B-CITY
iz O
Indije B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Olivia B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
presented O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Sofia B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
in O
Reading B-CITY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Leon B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
u O
Edinburghu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
presented O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
in O
Dublin B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Samsung B-COMPANY
, O
Olivia B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Seoul B-CITY
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
and O
Camila B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
discussed O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Airbus B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Birmingham B-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
to O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
to O
visit O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Vancouver B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Visau B-COMPANY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Marin B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
iz O
Lisabonu B-CITY
u O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Nika B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
presented O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Sofia B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
in O
Paris B-CITY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
thanked O
Aria B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
for O
Spotify B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Reading B-CITY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
thanked O
Benjamin B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
for O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Shopify B-COMPANY
, O
Sophia B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Stockholm B-CITY
from O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Nvidiaa B-COMPANY
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Noah B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
about O
Tesla B-COMPANY
from O
Geneva B-CITY
, O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Ottawa B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
to O
Dublin B-CITY
to O
visit O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
sent O
BP B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Aiden B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
in O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Gabrijela B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Rimu B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Ivana B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
iz O
Splitu B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
thanked O
Noah B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
for O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Aiden B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Mila B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
about O
Google B-COMPANY
from O
Rome B-CITY
, O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
presented O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Benjamin B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
in O
Austin B-CITY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Oracleu B-COMPANY
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Paola B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
u O
Splitu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
. O

Mirna B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
visited O
Toronto B-CITY
in O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Roche B-COMPANY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
sent O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Mia B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
in O
Chicago B-CITY
. O

Isabella B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
sent O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Olivia B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
in O
Johannesburg B-CITY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Spotifyju B-COMPANY
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
to O
Munich B-CITY
to O
visit O
Meta B-COMPANY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Knez I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
San Mateo B-CITY
iz O
Finske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Shopifyju B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
HSBC B-COMPANY
, O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Ottawa B-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
presented O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
in O
Amsterdam B-CITY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Karla B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
iz O
Splitu B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
met O
Abigail B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
in O
Phoenix B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
discussed O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Miami B-CITY
, O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

William B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
thanked O
Liam B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
for O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Reading B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
visited O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
in O
India B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
SAP B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Shopify B-COMPANY
, O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Prague B-CITY
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Daniel B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Italy B-COUNTRY
to O
Chicago B-CITY
to O
visit O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Mia B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
about O
SAP B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Janko B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Varaždin B-CITY
iz O
Češke B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Teslau B-COMPANY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
San Mateo B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Pfizeru B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Zoran B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
iz O
Zagrebu B-CITY
u O
Brazila B-COUNTRY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
München B-CITY
u O
Australije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
thanked O
Aiden B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
for O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Tokyo B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Daniel B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
about O
Citi B-COMPANY
from O
Reading B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
joined O
Intel B-COMPANY
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Madrid B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Marin B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
o O
Teslau B-COMPANY
u O
Zagrebu B-CITY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Hong Kong B-CITY
u O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
joined O
Samsung B-COMPANY
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
and O
Sophia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
discussed O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Roche B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Helena B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
iz O
Puli B-CITY
u O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Barclaysa B-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Lisabon B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Metau B-COMPANY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
and O
Henry B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
discussed O
Intel B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
South B-COUNTRY
Africa I-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
to O
Sydney B-CITY
to O
visit O
Siemens B-COMPANY
. O

Kristina B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Zagrebu B-CITY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
Ella B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
discussed O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Miami B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Amelia B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
about O
Roche B-COMPANY
from O
Johannesburg B-CITY
, O
Australia B-COUNTRY
. O

Filip B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Rim B-CITY
u O
Indije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Metau B-COMPANY
. O

Josip B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Dublin B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
joined O
IBM B-COMPANY
in O
Miami B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
visited O
Berlin B-CITY
in O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
. O

Aria B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Mia B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
about O
TikTok B-COMPANY
from O
Lisbon B-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
IBM-u B-COMPANY
u O
Berlinu B-CITY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
and O
Jacob B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
discussed O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Visa B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Lisbon B-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Charlotte B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
flew O
from O
France B-COUNTRY
to O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
to O
visit O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Zürich B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Amazonu B-COMPANY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
visited O
Paris B-CITY
in O
India B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Oracle B-COMPANY
. O

Sofia B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
joined O
IBM B-COMPANY
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

William B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
and O
Abigail B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
discussed O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Shell B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Vancouver B-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
u O
Helsinkiju B-CITY
. O

James B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
to O
Seattle B-CITY
to O
visit O
Apple B-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Elijah B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
about O
HSBC B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
visited O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
in O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
. O

Lea B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Prag B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Rocheu B-COMPANY
. O

Marko B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ivana B-PERSON
Tomaš I-PERSON
u O
Vancouveru B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
. O

Kristijan B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Ivana B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
u O
Readingu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
. O

Aiden B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
sent O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Alexander B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
in O
Helsinki B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
, O
Luna B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Lausanne B-CITY
from O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
joined O
Siemens B-COMPANY
in O
Austin B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
i O
Nika B-PERSON
Marić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Puli B-CITY
u O
Nizozemske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Googleu B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Airbus B-COMPANY
, O
Amelia B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
moved O
to O
London B-CITY
from O
Ireland B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
San Mateo B-CITY
iz O
Ujedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Arapskih I-COUNTRY
Emirata I-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Metau B-COMPANY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Berlin B-CITY
iz O
Češke B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Siemensu B-COMPANY
. O

Prema O
SAP B-COMPANY
, O
Filip B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Rijeka B-CITY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
thanked O
Sophia B-PERSON
Perez I-PERSON
for O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
. O

Petra B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Luka B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
o O
SAP-u B-COMPANY
u O
Sydneyu B-CITY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Wright I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Michael B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
about O
Samsung B-COMPANY
from O
Dublin B-CITY
, O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Matthew B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Abigail B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
about O
BP B-COMPANY
from O
London B-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

Dora B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
i O
Andrej B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
u O
Japana B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Spotifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
joined O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
in O
Amsterdam B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
to O
Boston B-CITY
to O
visit O
Visa B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
, O
Jackson B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
moved O
to O
London B-CITY
from O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Applea B-COMPANY
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Hernandez I-PERSON
and O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
discussed O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Petar B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
iz O
New Yorku B-CITY
u O
Australije B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
SAP B-COMPANY
, O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Amsterdam B-CITY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Accentureu B-COMPANY
u O
Londonu B-CITY
. O

Mila B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
visited O
Paris B-CITY
in O
Japan B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
i O
Leon B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
u O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Boeingu B-COMPANY
. O

Dora B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Tokio B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Janko B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
u O
Šibeniku B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Španjolske B-COUNTRY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
and O
Sofia B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
discussed O
Google B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Citi B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Madrid B-CITY
, O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

James B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
thanked O
Mia B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
for O
UBS B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Stockholm B-CITY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
joined O
Boeing B-COMPANY
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Sweden B-COUNTRY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
to O
Phoenix B-CITY
to O
visit O
Oracle B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Visa B-COMPANY
, O
Matthew B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Barcelona B-CITY
from O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Lovrić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Mario B-PERSON
Jerković I-PERSON
o O
Shellu B-COMPANY
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
visited O
Paris B-CITY
in O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
flew O
from O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
to O
Vancouver B-CITY
to O
visit O
IBM B-COMPANY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marta B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
u O
Varaždinu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
BP B-COMPANY
, O
Isabella B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Župan I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Kristina B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Infobipa B-COMPANY
u O
Splitu B-CITY
. O

Olivia B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
presented O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Michael B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
in O
Boston B-CITY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Rim B-CITY
iz O
Indije B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Intelu B-COMPANY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Australia B-COUNTRY
to O
Manchester B-CITY
to O
visit O
Samsung B-COMPANY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
New York B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Accentureu B-COMPANY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
met O
Camila B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
in O
Berlin B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
. O

Alexander B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
thanked O
James B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
for O
Samsung B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Manchester B-CITY
. O

Mia B-PERSON
White I-PERSON
visited O
Austin B-CITY
in O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Roche B-COMPANY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
München B-CITY
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Amazonu B-COMPANY
u O
Pragu B-CITY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Infobipa B-COMPANY
u O
Ženevi B-CITY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Elijah B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
about O
TikTok B-COMPANY
from O
Seoul B-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Liam B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
about O
Pfizer B-COMPANY
from O
Zurich B-CITY
, O
Finland B-COUNTRY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Sara B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Australije B-COUNTRY
. O

Michael B-PERSON
King I-PERSON
sent O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Oliver B-PERSON
Jackson I-PERSON
in O
Toulouse B-CITY
. O

According O
to O
BP B-COMPANY
, O
Charlotte B-PERSON
Anderson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Dublin B-CITY
from O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
London B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Bogdan I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Oraclea B-COMPANY
u O
Varaždinu B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Rijeka B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Shopifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
thanked O
Luna B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
for O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Dublin B-CITY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
thanked O
James B-PERSON
Allen I-PERSON
for O
Amazon B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Birmingham B-CITY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Helsinki B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Metau B-COMPANY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
u O
Stockholmu B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
i O
Petar B-PERSON
Krpan I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Puli B-CITY
u O
Meksika B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Intelu B-COMPANY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
i O
Marta B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Madridu B-CITY
u O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Visau B-COMPANY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
about O
Tesla B-COMPANY
from O
Seoul B-CITY
, O
India B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Netflix B-COMPANY
, O
Ava B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Phoenix B-CITY
from O
Japan B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Citia B-COMPANY
, O
Matija B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Hong Kong B-CITY
. O

Mario B-PERSON
Kolar I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Helsinki B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Oracleu B-COMPANY
. O

Benjamin B-PERSON
Walker I-PERSON
visited O
Munich B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
HSBC B-COMPANY
. O

Leon B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
i O
Ela B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
u O
Hrvatske B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Boeingu B-COMPANY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Airbusa B-COMPANY
u O
Puli B-CITY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Matea B-PERSON
Kovačević I-PERSON
u O
Puli B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Ujedinjenog B-COUNTRY
Kraljevstva I-COUNTRY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
presented O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Evelyn B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
in O
Seattle B-CITY
. O

Elizabeth B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
visited O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
in O
Japan B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Oracle B-COMPANY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Aria B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
about O
Shopify B-COMPANY
from O
Zurich B-CITY
, O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Luna B-PERSON
Taylor I-PERSON
and O
Abigail B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
discussed O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Airbnb B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
, O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Avery B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
met O
Lucas B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
in O
Edinburgh B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Nika B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Vancouver B-CITY
u O
Ujedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Arapskih I-COUNTRY
Emirata I-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Shopifyju B-COMPANY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Czech B-COUNTRY
Republic I-COUNTRY
to O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
to O
visit O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
je O
zahvalio O
Lucija B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
na O
podršci O
Samsunga B-COMPANY
u O
Osijeku B-CITY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Kristijan B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
iz O
Ženevi B-CITY
u O
Njemačke B-COUNTRY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Hong Kong B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Jelena B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Madrid B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Nestléu B-COMPANY
. O

William B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
sent O
Netflix B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Emily B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
in O
Seoul B-CITY
. O

Marija B-PERSON
Prskalo I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Tokio B-CITY
u O
Australije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Samsungu B-COMPANY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
presented O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Harper B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Italy B-COUNTRY
to O
Prague B-CITY
to O
visit O
SAP B-COMPANY
. O

Noah B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
presented O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Garcia I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
visited O
Austin B-CITY
in O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Wilson I-PERSON
presented O
OpenAI B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Michael B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
in O
Seattle B-CITY
. O

Sebastian B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
about O
Netflix B-COMPANY
from O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
. O

Logan B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
presented O
Deloitte B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Luna B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
in O
Paris B-CITY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Jurković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Dubrovniku B-CITY
. O

Ante B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Deloittea B-COMPANY
u O
Madridu B-CITY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Miller I-PERSON
presented O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Charlotte B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Jurić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Visaa B-COMPANY
u O
Dublinu B-CITY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Switzerland B-COUNTRY
to O
Madrid B-CITY
to O
visit O
Tesla B-COMPANY
. O

Liam B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
flew O
from O
Spain B-COUNTRY
to O
San B-CITY
Francisco I-CITY
to O
visit O
Shopify B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
presented O
Apple B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Harper B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
in O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
. O

Emily B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Avery B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
about O
Google B-COMPANY
from O
Paris B-CITY
, O
Brazil B-COUNTRY
. O

Matija B-PERSON
Radić I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Mirna B-PERSON
Tuškan I-PERSON
iz O
Münchenu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
. O

Ela B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Infobipu B-COMPANY
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Mitchell I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Camila B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
about O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
from O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
, O
Spain B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Siemensa B-COMPANY
, O
Mario B-PERSON
Majstorović I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Tokio B-CITY
. O

Dora B-PERSON
Rogić I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Marija B-PERSON
Horvat I-PERSON
u O
Parizu B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Finske B-COUNTRY
. O

Matea B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Varaždin B-CITY
u O
Kanade B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
obišao O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobilima I-COMPANY
. O

Ethan B-PERSON
Clark I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Abigail B-PERSON
Thompson I-PERSON
about O
Citi B-COMPANY
from O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Ana B-PERSON
Pavlović I-PERSON
je O
posjetio O
Beč B-CITY
i O
razgovarao O
o O
Airbusu B-COMPANY
. O

Prema O
Shopifya B-COMPANY
, O
Sara B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Johannesburg B-CITY
. O

Andrej B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Reading B-CITY
iz O
Sjedinjenih B-COUNTRY
Država I-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
. O

Jackson B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
visited O
Tokyo B-CITY
in O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Siemens B-COMPANY
. O

James B-PERSON
Nelson I-PERSON
thanked O
Sophia B-PERSON
Carter I-PERSON
for O
TikTok B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Sydney B-CITY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Pavić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Lea B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
o O
BP-u B-COMPANY
u O
Varaždinu B-CITY
. O

Mila B-PERSON
Moore I-PERSON
presented O
Siemens B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Matthew B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
in O
Rome B-CITY
. O

Evelyn B-PERSON
Rodriguez I-PERSON
presented O
Atlassian B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Elijah B-PERSON
Green I-PERSON
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
. O

Dario B-PERSON
Barišić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Rochea B-COMPANY
u O
Lausannei B-CITY
. O

Nikola B-PERSON
Perković I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Visaa B-COMPANY
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
. O

Abigail B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
thanked O
William B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
for O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Denver B-CITY
. O

Mason B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
thanked O
Sebastian B-PERSON
Brown I-PERSON
for O
Visa B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Hong B-CITY
Kong I-CITY
. O

Paola B-PERSON
Novak I-PERSON
je O
razgovarao O
s O
Kristina B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
u O
Rijeci B-CITY
nakon O
povratka O
iz O
Švicarske B-COUNTRY
. O

Prema O
Oraclea B-COMPANY
, O
Tomislav B-PERSON
Lončar I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Prag B-CITY
. O

Prema O
Rimac B-COMPANY
Automobila I-COMPANY
, O
Ivana B-PERSON
Šarić I-PERSON
se O
preselio O
u O
Lisabon B-CITY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Johnson I-PERSON
thanked O
Aria B-PERSON
Young I-PERSON
for O
Airbus B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
London B-CITY
. O

Lucija B-PERSON
Kovačić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Accenturea B-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Alexander B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
about O
Tesla B-COMPANY
from O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
Kingdom I-COUNTRY
. O

Ava B-PERSON
Hill I-PERSON
presented O
Meta B-COMPANY
's O
proposal O
to O
Henry B-PERSON
Baker I-PERSON
in O
Toulouse B-CITY
. O

Jacob B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
joined O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
in O
Seattle B-CITY
after O
leaving O
Mexico B-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Lopez I-PERSON
met O
Elijah B-PERSON
Roberts I-PERSON
in O
Madrid B-CITY
after O
returning O
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Gabrijela B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
i O
Ante B-PERSON
Orešković I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
Amsterdamu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Barclaysu B-COMPANY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Babić I-PERSON
je O
pregovarao O
s O
Janko B-PERSON
Petrović I-PERSON
o O
Boeingu B-COMPANY
u O
Pragu B-CITY
. O

Lucas B-PERSON
Robinson I-PERSON
visited O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
in O
Germany B-COUNTRY
for O
an O
interview O
at O
Barclays B-COMPANY
. O

Matej B-PERSON
Vidić I-PERSON
je O
dostavio O
uzorke O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Dublinu B-CITY
. O

Ivana B-PERSON
Perić I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupi I-COMPANY
u O
Tokiju B-CITY
. O

Lea B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
nazvao O
Janko B-PERSON
Cvitković I-PERSON
iz O
Pragu B-CITY
u O
Švedske B-COUNTRY
. O

Luka B-PERSON
Kovač I-PERSON
je O
poslao O
izvještaj O
Googleu B-COMPANY
u O
Splitu B-CITY
. O

Emma B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
joined O
Airbus B-COMPANY
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
after O
leaving O
Italy B-COUNTRY
. O

Marin B-PERSON
Blažević I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Spotifya B-COMPANY
u O
Zürichu B-CITY
. O

Henry B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
and O
Elijah B-PERSON
Martin I-PERSON
discussed O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
and O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Ottawa B-CITY
, O
United B-COUNTRY
States I-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Nvidia B-COMPANY
, O
Emma B-PERSON
Lee I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Munich B-CITY
from O
United B-COUNTRY
Arab I-COUNTRY
Emirates I-COUNTRY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Vuković I-PERSON
je O
stigao O
u O
Beč B-CITY
iz O
Francuske B-COUNTRY
na O
sastanak O
u O
Podravkau B-COMPANY
. O

According O
to O
Microsoft B-COMPANY
, O
Alexander B-PERSON
Martinez I-PERSON
moved O
to O
Geneva B-CITY
from O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Oliver B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
wrote O
to O
Jackson B-PERSON
Thomas I-PERSON
about O
Samsung B-COMPANY
from O
Denver B-CITY
, O
Canada B-COUNTRY
. O

Sophia B-PERSON
Harris I-PERSON
and O
Elizabeth B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
discussed O
Accenture B-COMPANY
's O
and O
HSBC B-COMPANY
's O
plans O
in O
Berlin B-CITY
, O
Germany B-COUNTRY
. O

According O
to O
Vodafone B-COMPANY
, O
Jackson B-PERSON
Davis I-PERSON
moved O
to O
New B-CITY
York I-CITY
from O
Netherlands B-COUNTRY
. O

Aiden B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
thanked O
Liam B-PERSON
Smith I-PERSON
for O
Barclays B-COMPANY
's O
support O
in O
Los B-CITY
Angeles I-CITY
. O

Camila B-PERSON
Lewis I-PERSON
sent O
Nestlé B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
Avery B-PERSON
Hall I-PERSON
in O
Miami B-CITY
. O

Tea B-PERSON
Šimić I-PERSON
je O
predstavio O
planove O
Atlantic B-COMPANY
Grupe I-COMPANY
u O
Ottawi B-CITY
. O

Amelia B-PERSON
Adams I-PERSON
sent O
Boeing B-COMPANY
's O
report O
to O
William B-PERSON
Scott I-PERSON
in O
Chicago B-CITY
. O

Karla B-PERSON
Krstić I-PERSON
i O
Marin B-PERSON
Vukelić I-PERSON
su O
se O
sreli O
u O
San Mateu B-CITY
u O
Austrije B-COUNTRY
kako O
bi O
razgovarali O
o O
Metau B-COMPANY
. O
